http://www.lwgc.co.uk/privacy-policy

HomeThe Course Explore
Hole-by-Hole Tour360 Sky ViewCourse photosScorecardCourse ReviewsSafety Notice The Club Discover
Become a MemberThe Club ProClub NewsThe ClubhouseEvent Calendar Contact usMeeting/Conference roomCome & Play Playing Options
Llandrindod Wells Golf Club Privacy Policy
This privacy policy explains how Llandrindod Wells Golf Club protects and manages any personal data that you give us and that we hold about you.
Llandrindod Wells Golf Club is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. You can be assured that any personal information you provide us with will only be used in accordance with this privacy policy.
What information do we collect about you?
We collect information about you when you join Llandrindod Wells Golf Club or voluntarily sign up to receive our discounted offers via our website. We collect only the information required from you to be able to fulfill our contractual obligations which includes being able to contact you to be able to send Subscription Renewals, AGM notices, Latest Club News, Visitors Offers and to administer competitions at the Club.
How your information about you will be used?
We use the information collected to allow us to fulfil our contractual obligations to you as a member, which will include contacting you by post. In order to fulfil our contractual obligations, to you as a member, we share your information with external and internal data processors (ClubV1 ,our Membership Administration System, MailChimp ,our email marketing provider). Your personal data is administered internally by the clubs Data Controller who adheres to the Golf Clubs internal data protection policies and procedures.
Marketing
We would also like to be able to correspond with you regarding our activities, including events and competitions by way of post, telephone and email. We don’t share your data with external marketing companies who would contact you this way. If you have consented to this correspondence you can opt out at any time by contacting us at This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it., or by writing to Llandrindod Wells Golf Club, Golf Links Road, Llandrindod Wells, Powys, LD1 5NY.
Individual Rights
You have the right to request a copy of the information we hold about you. If you would like a copy of this information, please email us or write to the club (contact details above).We want to make sure that your personal information is accurate and up to date. You may ask us to correct or erase information that you think is inaccurate. At the time of collecting data you have the right to object to the Club holding certain information about you.
back to top
Upcoming Events12.12.20
Ladies Winter League & Christmas Lunch
Read More...
13.12.20
Winter League
Read More...
19.12.20
Christmas Jumper Competition
Read More...
Please familiarise yourself with our privacy policy.
I accept
Read more
